<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Kult of the Cyber Witch - errbufferoverfl</title><link href="https://KotCW.github.io.git/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://KotCW.github.io.git/feeds/errbufferoverfl.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://KotCW.github.io.git/</id><updated>2018-01-09T00:00:00+11:00</updated><entry><title>Code of Conduct</title><link href="https://KotCW.github.io.git/coc.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-01-09T00:00:00+11:00</published><updated>2018-01-09T00:00:00+11:00</updated><author><name>errbufferoverfl</name></author><id>tag:kotcw.github.io.git,2018-01-09:/coc.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Everybody who participates in Kult of the Cyber Witch in one way or another is required to conform to this Code of Conduct 
(CoC). This includes attendees, contributors, sponsors, organisers and volunteers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The CoC applies before and throughout the event (including related activities such as social events, and social media …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Everybody who participates in Kult of the Cyber Witch in one way or another is required to conform to this Code of Conduct 
(CoC). This includes attendees, contributors, sponsors, organisers and volunteers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The CoC applies before and throughout the event (including related activities such as social events, and social media).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Why do we have a Code of Conduct?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our goals with having this Code of Conduct are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping everyone feel safe and included. We want to set the expectation that harassment and other unpleasant behaviour 
are not acceptable. So that if people do have an unpleasant experience, they know that’s not neither the norm nor 
acceptable to us as a community.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helping to build trust that if an incident is reported, we will not respond with victim blaming, and that we will 
do a thorough investigation. Even, for example, if the incident concerns someone in a position of power.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Informing everyone of the expected behaviour. We are a diverse community, and having a Code of Conduct makes the 
expectations of everybody’s behaviour explicit and transparent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Having a framework for report handling. The Code of Conduct is the basis for dealing with a report, assessing 
whether the CoC was violated, and what action should be taken.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Our Code of Conduct&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be kind and considerate to others. Do not insult or put down other attendees. Behave professionally.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are dedicated to providing a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of race, ethnicity, 
culture, national origin, colour, immigration status, social and economic class, educational level, sex, 
sexual orientation, gender identity and expression, age, size, family status, political belief, religion, 
and mental and physical ability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We do not tolerate harassment of participants in any form. This includes offensive comments related 
to the categories above, deliberate intimidation, stalking, following, harassing photography or recording, 
sustained disruption of talks or other events, violent threats or language, inappropriate physical contact, 
and unwelcome sexual attention. Advocating for, or encouraging, any of the above behaviour is also not acceptable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sexual language and imagery are not appropriate for any venue to which the CoC applies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don’t publish individual photographs of people without their consent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be careful in the words that you choose. Remember that sexist, racist, and other exclusionary jokes can be 
offensive and unwelcoming to those around you. Excessive swearing and offensive jokes are not appropriate for 
Kult of the Cyber Witch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Where does the Code of Conduct apply?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Code of Conduct applies to all Kult of the Cyber Witch related spaces. That includes, but is not limited to:
&lt;em&gt; Any venue related social activities
&lt;/em&gt; Slack channels, tweets with the zine hashtag, and other online media&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Code of Conduct does not exclusively apply to events on the publication agenda. For example, if after a 
scheduled social event you go to a bar with a group of fellow participants, and someone harasses you there, 
we would still treat that as a CoC violation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What can happen if the CoC is violated?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In case of a Code of Conduct violation, some of the most common actions organisers may take are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demanding that a participant stops their behaviour.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demanding that a participant prevents further contact with certain other participants.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not publishing submitted work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Removing their work from any current or future publications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Removing a participant from the community.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The action taken is at the discretion of the Code of Conduct team. Participants are expected to comply 
immediately, and further action may be taken in case a participant does not comply. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A record will be kept of all incidents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Where to report incidents&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If a Code of Conduct incident happens to you, or witness it happening to someone else, please contact the CoC team 
immediately either in person, or by sending an email to 
&lt;a href="mailto:conduct@kultofthecyberwitch.org"&gt;conduct@kultofthecyberwitch.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Guidelines for reporting incidents&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please do not feel like you may be a burden to us by reporting incidents. Even if you happen to report multiple 
incidents. We rather consider reports an opportunity for us to act: by knowing about an incident, we can act on it, 
and often prevent it from continuing or repeating. But if we don’t know, we can’t take action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are not sure whether the situation was a Code of Conduct violation, or whether it applied to that particular 
space, we encourage you to still report it. We would much rather have a few extra reports where we decide to take 
no action, rather than miss a report of an actual violation. We do not look negatively on you if we find the incident 
is not a violation. And knowing about incidents that are not violations, or happen outside our spaces, can also help 
us to improve the Code of Conduct or the processes surrounding it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In your report please include, when possible:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your contact info (so we can get in touch with you)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Names (real, nicknames, or pseudonyms) of any individuals involved. If there were other witnesses besides you, 
please try to include them as well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When and where the incident occurred. Please be as specific as possible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your account of what occurred. If there is a written record (e.g. tweets or slack messages) please include 
screenshots, or otherwise a link.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Any extra context you believe existed for the incident.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you believe this incident is ongoing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Any other information you believe we should have.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you don’t have some of this information, or not at this time, please still make the report anyways.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When handling a report, we follow specific guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Code of Conduct has been borrowed and updated from &lt;a href="https://2018.djangocon.eu/conduct/"&gt;Django Con Europe 2018&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>Conjure an Administrator</title><link href="https://KotCW.github.io.git/conjure.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-01-09T00:00:00+11:00</published><updated>2018-01-09T00:00:00+11:00</updated><author><name>errbufferoverfl</name></author><id>tag:kotcw.github.io.git,2018-01-09:/conjure.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;h2&gt;Accessibility&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have attempted to make this website as accessible as possible to all users. If you would like to report an
accessibility issue please contact 
&lt;a href="mailto:accessibility@kultofthecyberwitch.org?Subject=Report%20an%20Accessibity%20Issue"&gt;accessibility (at) kultofthecyberwitch (dot) org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;General Enquiries&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to get in contact for a chat or just find out more please contact …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;Accessibility&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have attempted to make this website as accessible as possible to all users. If you would like to report an
accessibility issue please contact 
&lt;a href="mailto:accessibility@kultofthecyberwitch.org?Subject=Report%20an%20Accessibity%20Issue"&gt;accessibility (at) kultofthecyberwitch (dot) org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;General Enquiries&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to get in contact for a chat or just find out more please contact 
&lt;a href="mailto:general@kultofthecyberwitch.org?Subject=General%20Enquiry"&gt;general (at) kultofthecyberwitch (dot) org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Privacy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you find a privacy issue or wish to speak to us about out Privacy Policy please contact &lt;a href="mailto:privacy@kultofthecyberwitch.org?Subject=Report%20a%20Privacy%20Issue"&gt;privacy (at) kultofthecyberwitch (dot) org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Security&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you find a security issue please contact &lt;a href="mailto:security@kultofthecyberwitch.org?Subject=Report%20a%20Security%20Issue"&gt;security (at) kultofthecyberwitch (dot) org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Slack&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you wish to join our Slack community contact us at &lt;a href="mailto:slack@kultofthecyberwitch.org?Subject=Request%20a%20Slack%20Invite"&gt;slack (at) kultofthecyberwitch (dot) org&lt;/a&gt; or direct message
&lt;code&gt;@errbufferoverfl&lt;/code&gt; on Twitter.&lt;/p&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>errbufferoverfl Profile</title><link href="https://KotCW.github.io.git/errbufferoverfl-profile.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-01-09T00:00:00+11:00</published><updated>2018-01-09T00:00:00+11:00</updated><author><name>errbufferoverfl</name></author><id>tag:kotcw.github.io.git,2018-01-09:/errbufferoverfl-profile.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;errbufferoverfl is a “white rabbit” hacker by day and a Python developer by night, she loves 
good looking code, poisonous plants and spending time dreaming up new security tools that 
eventually (someday) get published. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She suffers a chronic case of refactoring syndrome 
and checklist-itis. In her post-hacker life she worked …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;errbufferoverfl is a “white rabbit” hacker by day and a Python developer by night, she loves 
good looking code, poisonous plants and spending time dreaming up new security tools that 
eventually (someday) get published. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She suffers a chronic case of refactoring syndrome 
and checklist-itis. In her post-hacker life she worked for SaaS providers trying to make 
information security and policy more accessible and fun, giving workshops on lock-picking and 
vulnerability management. If left unattended too long she will resume her Pavlovian-style training 
to get people to improve security practices. Her favourite member of One-Direction is the one with 
the best passwords.&lt;/p&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>Privacy Policy for Kult of the Cyber Witch</title><link href="https://KotCW.github.io.git/privacy.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-01-09T00:00:00+11:00</published><updated>2018-01-09T00:00:00+11:00</updated><author><name>errbufferoverfl</name></author><id>tag:kotcw.github.io.git,2018-01-09:/privacy.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;At Kult of the Cyber Witch, accessible from kultofthecyberwitch.org and kotcw.org, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Kult of the Cyber Witch and how we use it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;At Kult of the Cyber Witch, accessible from kultofthecyberwitch.org and kotcw.org, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Kult of the Cyber Witch and how we use it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us through email at &lt;a href="mailto:privacy@kultofthecyberwitch.org?Subject=Report%20a%20Privacy%20Issue"&gt;privacy (at) kultofthecyberwitch (dot) org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Log Files&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kult of the Cyber Witch follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analysing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Privacy Policies&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Kult of the Cyber Witch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Kult of the Cyber Witch, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that Kult of the Cyber Witch has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Third Pary Privacy Policies&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kult of the Cyber Witch's Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. You may find a complete list of these Privacy Policies and their links here: Privacy Policy Links.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites. What Are Cookies?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Children's Information&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kult of the Cyber Witch does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Online Privacy Policy Only&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This privacy policy (created with the GDPR Generator) applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Kult of the Cyber Witch. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Consent&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.&lt;/p&gt;</content></entry></feed>